Welcome home.
So it wasn't a dream after all.
Master! Master!
Today we should register you as my master.
Just insert your finger into my va—
Not right now!
First, we need to get you some
actual clothes and underwear.
Then we're already halfway there.
Yeah, but you look like a cosplayer!
But with that said...
There's nothing for you to wear.
Well, it's still early, so I'm going to the store.
You're heading out?
I'll go with you.
Absolutely not!
You can't just go out commando!
But I've been cooped up in here ever since I arrived.
I get so lonely.
Are you tired, Master?
Don't call me "Master" when we're out.
So windy!
It's quite windy today, huh?
Are you okay, Master?
No, I'm not okay!
Come on, the store's right there.
Okay!
Thanks for coming.
Okay, we got some undies.
Now to find somewhere
for her to put them on and head home.
Blocked!
Like I said, eye contact is not a signal to kiss me!
Understood.
Here, go in there and put them on.
Sure. I'll be right back.
Surely she at least knows
her way around a restroom.
Why is she still in there?!
Hey! You all right?
Master...
Please come in.
BEWARE OF
PERVERTS!
Let's do your master registration here.
BEWARE OF
PERVERTS!
Huh?
BEWARE OF
PERVERTS!
I won't move unless you do it.
BEWARE OF
PERVERTS!
Huh? What do you—
Master...
Fine, but put the panties on first.
Please do it for me, Master.
Huh?!
Right, well, raise your right leg.
I...
I want to be able to serve you
as soon as possible, Master.
Some of my functions
are unavailable until you register.
I cannot satisfy you in this state, Master!
Make me...
Make me yours and yours alone.
Excuse me!
Oh!
Sorry! I'll be right out!
I nearly got caught up in the heat of the moment.
I'm looking forward to having you take off
the underwear you got for me, Master.
I'm going on ahead!
Master!
Still...
Having someone else around isn't all that bad.
Master, what did you just—
Nothing! Just forget it! Why are you so fast?!